# **KUNAL SHIVANKAR**

#### **Automation Test Engineer**

+91 8999108121

kunalshivankar19@gmail.com

8

https://kunalshivankar.github.io/Portfolio/

# **SUMMARY**

Dedicated QA and Test Engineer with 2.5+ Year of Strong Experience in test Automation using selenium with java in agile methodology. Good knowledge of software development lifecycle that includes requirement analysis, designing test scenarios, testing, review.

## **SKILLS**

Seleniun	n Java	SQL	Git Hub	Maven	JIRA	Postman	TestNo	G Cucumber
Automation testing		TDD	GitLab	BDD	JIRA	TestNG	JMeter	Manual Testing
CI/CD	API testing	Per	formance T	esting				

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Software Test Engineer

#### **Mastersoft ERP Solutions Pvt.Ltd**

## 04/2023 - Present

Nagpui

MasteSoft provides ERP e-governance solution to all types of educational institution serving more than 2000 institute.

- · Created Selenium Test cases for automation using Selenium Web Driver and Java.
- · Worked with developers to identify, document and track defects in the system.
- Create detailed load and performance test plans and scripts to simulate user behavior and application load using tools such as JMeter, LoadRunner, or similar.
- Working closely with Product Management, QA Lead, Development Team and Support teams to produce comprehensive testing and deliver a quality-focused OA deliverable.
- · Execute automated tests, analyze results, and report defects. Track and manage defects to resolution using tools like JIRA, or similar.
- Participated in Client Calls for better understanding.
- Working as part of a team to design, develop, execute and maintain manual and automated well structured test plans, test design for applications based on user stories/requirements and map test case requirements and design test
- Collaborate with QA, development, and product teams to understand requirements and design comprehensive test plans and strategies.
- Develop and maintain test frameworks to support continuous integration and delivery CI/CD pipelines.

#### **QA** Tester

## Moxiedeck Software Pvt Ltd

**iii** 06/2022 - 04/2023

**Q** Pune

efficiently delivers creative communications, interactive web solutions and digital marketing services to its global customers

- Develop detailed, comprehensive, and well-structured test plans and test cases based on requirements and specifications.
- Execute manual tests on web, mobile, and desktop applications to identify and document defects.
- Develop and execute automated test scripts as needed.
- · Identify, document, and track defects and issues found during testing using bug tracking tools (e.g., Jira, Bug-Tracker).
- Create and maintain test documentation, including test cases, test scripts, and test data.
- Execute test cases (manual) and identify defects during testing.
- · Assist in the coordination and execution of UAT, working closely with stakeholders to ensure requirements are met.

## **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor of Engineering

Yeshwantrao Chavan College of Engineering

**=** 2019 - 2022

# **PROJECTS**

#### **RF Campus**

# 04/2023-Present

Nagpur

RF Campus is a complete Education ERP solution provided to autonomous colleges it includes various private Engineering colleges and NIT's over all India.